<resource type="customer-quotes" xmlns="http://tradeconfo.com/ns/api">

	<description>
		Represent a set of terms and conditions for a single currency quote.
	</description>

	<comment>
		<ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
			<li>A valid customer-quote-request MUST contain one or more customer-quote
				resources.</li>
			<li>The initial customer-quote-request resource that POSTed to the
				service by a
				client application MUST contains either a positive remittance-amount attribute
				or a
				positive delivery-amount attribute but NOT both. The service will ignore
				any null or zero values for these attributes</li>
			<li>Each customer-quote resource MUST reference a remittance-currency and MUST
				reference either a delivery-currency or a
				beneficiary but NOT both.</li>
			<li>If the customer accepts a customer-quote-request the server will execute
				the least number of fx-transactions required to fulfil that requests related
				customer-quotes.
			</li>
			<li>If the customer accepts a customer-quote-request that contains
				customer-quotes referencing a beneficiary then
				server will enter a
				payment-instruction for the delivery-amount to each such beneficiary.</li>
		</ul>
	</comment>

	<attribute name="remittance-amount" type="currency-amount" required="true" />
	<attribute name="remittance-fee" type="currency-amount" required="false" />
	<attribute name="remittance-information" type="string" required="false">
		<comment>
			Message intended for the beneficiary. Limited to 35 characters.
		</comment>
	</attribute>
	<attribute name="delivery-amount" type="currency-amount" required="true" />
	<attribute name="delivery-fee" type="currency-amount" required="false" />
	<attribute name="deliverable" type="boolean" required="false" />
	<attribute name="settlement-time" type="timestamp" required="false" />
	<attribute name="value-date" type="date" required="false" />
	<attribute name="status" type="enum" enum="customer.quotes.status"
		required="true"
	>
		<comment>
			The tradeable status of this quote. This quote may only be accepted by
			the customer when the value of this attribute is TRADEABLE.
		</comment>
	</attribute>
	<attribute name="comment" type="string" required="false">
		<comment>
			May contain additional info as to why this quote's status is not
			TRADEABLE.
		</comment>
	</attribute>
	<attribute name="reason-comment" type="string" required="false">
		<comment>
			If a payment-reason is present additional information MAY be provided to
			facilitate compliance checking.
		</comment>
	</attribute>

	<relationship name="remittance-currency" resource="currencies"
		required="true"
	>
		<comment>
			Currency the customer will remit to the domain.
		</comment>
	</relationship>
	<relationship name="delivery-currency" resource="currencies"
		required="true"
	>
		<comment>
			Currency the domain will deliver on behalf of the customer.
		</comment>
	</relationship>
	<relationship name="beneficiary" resource="bank-accounts" required="true">
		<comment>
			The bank account to which the domain will deliver currency on behalf
			of
			the customer.
		</comment>
	</relationship>
	<relationship name="payment-reason" resource="payment-reason"
		required="false"
	>
		<comment>
			If beneficiary is present a reason for the resulting payment MAY be
			provided to
			facilitate compliance checking.
		</comment>
	</relationship>

</resource>
